Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - News, Cecil Brown, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
    - News, Bill Henry, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
    - News, Cecil Brown, 1942 Dec. 23
      [See reel 174 for rest of 1942]
  - Ward Baking Co.
    [See also reels 170, 171, 175]
    - Audition (Tip Top Bread), spot announcements, 1943 June 21
    - Spot announcements, Tip Top Bread, 1943 July 16
    - Commercials, Enriched Tip Top Bread, Terry and the Pirates, 1942 Apr.-Sept.
    - Commercials, Enriched Tip Top Bread, Judy and Jane, 1943 Jan.-Mar.
    - Commercials, Enriched Tip Top Bread, Judy and Jane, 1943 Mar.-July (Reel 207)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 June 21
  - J.B. Williams
    - Glider, Aqua Velva, commercials, 1942 Jan.-Sept., 1943 Mar.-Sept.
    - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1943 Jan.-June
    - Glider, Aqua Velva, Nero Wolf, 1943 Apr.-Sept.
    - Frank Sinatra, commercials, 1943 Dec.
    - Wm. L. Shirer, 1943 Dec.
  - Wm. Wrigley Jr. (Doublemint gum)
    - Gene Autry Show, 1941 Jan.-Aug.
      [See also reels 169-171; see reel 169 for Feb. 23 broadcast]
    - Gene Autry Show, 1941 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 208)
      [Missing Oct. 5, Nov. 9 broadcasts; see reels 169-170 for 1942 shows]
    - Gene Autry Show, 1943 Jan.-Aug.
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Raymond Clapper, commercials, London and Algeria broadcasts, 1943
      [See also reels 149, 150, 153, 170, 171, 175, 176]
  - Planter's Peanuts (Reel 209)
    - Commercials, 1943 Jan.-May
  - Fanny Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, 1942 Aug.-1943 Oct.
      [See also reels 170, 201]
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1942 Jan.-Apr.
    - Nelson Eddy, 1942 Apr.-Nov.
    - Nelson Eddy, 1942 Dec.-1943 Jan. (Reel 210)
    - Sammy Kaye and program, 1943
    - Bob Crosby and program, 1943 July-Dec.
      [See reel 214 for 1944]
    - Campus News, commercials, 1942 Oct.
    - Spot announcements, 1942 Jan.-Aug.
      [See also reel 188]
    - N.Y. Giants football, 1943 Oct.-Dec.
    - Commercials, Sports News with Bill Stern, 1942Oct.-1973 Jan., 1943 Aug.-Dec.
      [See reel 192 for 1943 Jan. 15-Aug. 27
    - Campus News, 1942 Oct.-1943 Jan.
      [See reel 192 for 1943 Jan.-Mar.]
    - Gloom Dodgers, 1942 Nov.-Dec.
      [See reel 192 for 1943 Jan.-Apr.
    - Gloom Dodgers (Reel 211)
      - commercials, 1942 Dec.-1943 Jan.
      - as broadcast, 1943 Mar. 8
      - commercials, 1943 Dec.-1944 June
    - Commercials, Sammy Kaye and program, Record of the Day, 1943 Jan.-May
      [Last week of April missing]
    - Spot announcements, 1942-1944
    - WHN Newsreel, 1942-1944
    - Fulton Lewis, 1942-1944
    - Vadenboncoeur, WSYR news, 1943-1944
    - Vadenboncoeur, WSYR news, 1944 Aug.-Nov. (Reel 212)
    - Red Barber, Gloom Dodgers, 1942 Nov.-1943 Jan.
    - Commercials, Racing News, Clem McCarthy, 1944 Oct.-Nov.
    - N.Y. Giants football play by play, 1943 Oct.-Dec.
      [See also reel 210]
    - Commercials, 1944 Oct.-Nov.
    - Sports Round Up, 1943 Sept.-1944 Nov.
      [Week of May 8 missing; see also reels 189, 192]
    - Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1943 Apr.-July
      [Brigg's Pipe Mixture also mentioned]
    - Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1943 July-Oct., 1944 Mar.-Aug. (Reel 213)
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 214)
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, etc., 1941 July-1943 Dec.
      [See also reels 178, 179, 204]
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard)
    - Brooklyn baseball, 1944 Aug.-Oct.
    - N.Y. Giants football, 1944 Oct.-Dec.
    - Bob Crosby, Les Tremayne, 1944 Jan.-June
      [See also reel 210 for 1943 broadcasts]
    - Andy Russell, Les Tremayne, etc., 1944 July
    - Andy Russell, Les Tremayne, etc., 1944 aug.-Oct. (Reel 215)
      [Edgar Bergen guest on Aug. 13]
    - Commercials, 1943 World Series, 1943
    - Allan Jones, Frankie Carle, etc., 1944 Apr.-Oct.
    - Sammy Kaye and program, 1944 Jan.-Mar.
      [Two pages missing from Mar. 8 broadcast; see reel 243 for Feb. 16 broadcast]
  - Carter's Products (Superin)
    - Commercials, 1944 Jan.-Feb.
  - Fleischmann's Vitamin Yeast tablets (Standard Brands)
    - Commercials, 1944 Oct. 5
  - United Hospital Fund
    - Edgar Bergen, Kate Smith, etc., 1944 Oct. 24
  - Auditions
    - Buxton, Schenectady production, 1944 Apr. 19
    - Planter's, The Peanut is a Serious Guy, 1944 May 24
      [See reels 170-171 for other auditions]
    - John Kuhne's script, 1944 Sept. 18
  - Scripts
    - Double Destiny, 1944 Dec. 27
    - Four Corners USA, 1944 Dec. 30
    - The Frank Sinatra program, 1944 July 6
    - King's Row, 1944 July 6-11
  - Ford Motors
    - Commercials, 1944 Apr.
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Commercials, 1944 June, Dec.
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Commercials, 1944 Dec. 28
  - Lever Brothers (Vimms)
    - Commercials, 1944 July
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Commercials, 1944 June
  - War Manpower Commission
    - Womanpower, 1944 May
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 234)
    [See also reels 133, 171, 199, 201]
    - Broadway Showtime, 1944
    - Broadway Showtime, commercials, 1943 Dec. 27
      [No broadcast June 12, Nov. 6; Sept. 18 broadcast never received]
  - Bank of America
    - Sunday Night Salute, 1944 Jan.-Mar.
      [See also reel 201]
  - Elgin National Watch Co.
    [See also reels 154, 170]
    - Adventures of Nero Wolfe, 1944 Jan.-May 12
      [Jan. 21 (#1) and June 30 (#24) never received from Chicago; Nero Wolfe also on J.B. Williams Co. program Apr.7-Sept. 27, 1943 (reel 207)]
    - Adventures of Nero Wolfe, 1944 May 19-July 14 (Reel 235)
  - Ford Motors
    - Stars of the Future, 1944 Dec.
      [See also reel 215]
  - Block Drug Co.
    - Gold Medal Capsules, spot announcements, 1944 Apr. 16
      [See also reels 171, 205]
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Bill Henry News, 1944
      [No broadcast July 11-21; see also reels 154-155, 170-171, 173-175, 206]
  - Kraft Cheese
    [See also reels 120-125, 127, 170, 177-179, 204-205, 214]
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, 1944 Jan.-Aug.
      [Missing Apr. 13, May 11, Oct. 26 broadcasts]
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 236)
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    [See also reels 31, 35, 102-110, 134-137, 153, 171, 182-186, 200-201, 215]
    - Hitch Hike--Aunt Jenny1944 Jan. 3
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1944 Jan.-July 3, Sept.
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 237)
  - Lever Brothers (Vimms)
    - Hitch Hike--Bright Horizons, 1944 Jan. 3
    - Frank Sinatra Program, 1944 Jan.-June, Aug-Dec.
      [Missing Sept. 20, Oct. 4 broadcasts]
  - Mentholatum
    - Mentholatum Mountaineers, 1944 Oct.-Dec.
      [See reel 174 for spots]
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    [See also reel 205]
    - Broadway Matinee, 1944 Jan.
    - Broadway Matinee, 1944 Jan.-July (Reel 238)
      [No broadcast on June 6 (D Day); see reel 259 for Apr. 7 and 14 broadcasts]
    - Broadway Matinee, 1944 July-Aug. (Reel 239)
    - Broadway Matinee, Fred Waring, 1944 Sept.-Dec.
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    [See also reel 210, 215]
    - What's New, 1944 Jan.-Feb.
    - The Music America Loves Best, 1944 Mar.-Dec.
      [Missing Oct. 15 broadcast]
  - Standard Brands
    - Chase & Sanborn, Edgar Bergen1944 Jan.-June
      [See also reels 93-99, 171, 202-204]
    - Chase & Sanborn, Gracie Fields, 1944 June-Aug.
    - Chase & Sanborn, Edgar Bergen1944 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 240)
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, Mary Marlin, 1944 Jan.-May 5
      [No broadcasts on June 6 (D Day), July 21]
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, Mary Marlin, 1944 May-Nov. (Reel 241)
    - Tenderleaf tea, Fleischmann's yeast, Mary Marlin, 1944 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 242)
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    [See also reels 149-153, 170-171, 175-176, 208, 215]
    - News, Henry Gladstone, 1944 Jan.-1945 Jan.
      [No broadcasts Mar. 23-June 12, 15; Sept. 21, Oct. 5 and 12, Nov. 2 and 6]
  - J.B. Williams
    - Glider, Aqua Velva, William L. Shirer News, commercials, 1944 Jan.-Nov.
      [Missing Mar. 19]
    - William L. Shirer News, commercials, 1944 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 243)
    - Latin American program, WLWO, commercials, 1941 July-1942 aug.
      [In Spanish; see also reel 182]
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - Commercials, NBC, 1942 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WEAF, 15 minute program, 1942 Mar.-Apr.
    - Commercials, WRC, Bruckhage News, 1942 Mar.
    - Commercials, WJSV, 15 minute program, 1942 Apr. 3
    - Commercials, WJSV, 1 minute, 1942 Jan.
    - Commercials, Westinghouse stations, Philadelphia, 15 minute program, 1942 Mar.
    - Commercials, WTIC, 15 minute program, 1941 Oct.-1942 Mar.
    - Commercials, WJAX, 5 minute, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar.
    - Commercials, WFLA, 5 minute, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar.
    - Commercials, WIOD, 5 minute, 1941 Nov.-Dec.
    - Commercials, WIOD, 15 minute program, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar.
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard)
    - Sammy Kaye, 1944 Feb. 16
      [See reel 215 for rest of broadcast]
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries
    - Nordic Fish, WWSW, 1931 Dec.-1932 Mar.
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol (Pyro)
    - WEAF, 1932 Oct.-Dec.
    - Boston, 1932 Oct.-Nov.
  - Seeck & Kade (Pertussin)
    - Frank Stretz and Orchestra, Spot announcements, KMBC, 1932 Jan.-Mar.
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby
    - The Libby Adventure Hour, 1934 Oct. 1
      [See also reels 155, 156, 170]
  - Nash Motors
    - Commercials, 1934
      [See also reel 12]
  - Emerson Drug Co. (Reel 244)
    - Bromo-Seltzer, Granlund and His Girls, 1935 July-1936 Jan.
      [Many missing]
    - Spot announcements, 1936 Feb.-1938 Apr.
    - Commercials, Donald Dickenson's program, 1938 Apr.-June
  - Andrew Jergens Co.
    - Ray Perkins, 1932 Jan.-May
      [See also reels 9, 10]
  - Pond's Creams
    [See also reels 28-30, 139, 158-159, 171, 201]
    - Afternoon Tea, commercials, 1930 Dec.
    - Leo Reisman and Orchestra, 1932
  - Nestlé
    [See also reels 11, 12]
    - Len Joy and Orchestra, Nestlé Chocolateers, 1932 Jan.-Sept.
    - Phil Spitalnyd and Orchestra, Nestlé Chocolateers, 1932 Oct.-Dec.
  - Lamont-Corliss (Danya)
    - Commercials, 1941 Dec.-1942 Apr.
      [See also reels 159, 170, 174]
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard)
    - Good Morning in Music, commercials, WJR, 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan.
    - Tommy Harmon Sports Review, commercials, WJR, 1941 Oct.-1942 Mar.
  - Standard Brands
    - Spot announcements, Royal Gelatin/desserts, KFBB, 1941 Dec.-1942 Apr.
    - Spot announcements, Tenderleaf Tea, KFBB, 1941 Oct.-1942 Apr.
    - Fleischmann Yeast, Rudy Vallee, 1930 Nov.-1931 Dec.
      [See also reels 20-25]
    - Baltimore Fleischmann's Yeast Hour, 1931 Jan.-Sept.
      [Missing Apr. 4, 11, 18, July 25]
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    - Peggy Winthrop, 1931 Oct.-Nov.
      [See also reels 102, 103; many broadcasts missing]
    - V.E. Meadows Beauty School, Lux Toilet Soap, no. 1-13, 1931 Aug.-Oct.
      [See reel 259 for Feb. 28 script]
    - Spot announcements, Lux Toilet Soap, 1942 Feb.-May
  - Ward Baking Co.
    - Enriched Tip Top Bread, Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Apr.
    - Enriched Tip Top Bread, Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Apr. (Reel 245)
    - Marjorie Mills, N.E. Network, 1942 Dec.-1943 Feb.
  - Mentholatum
    - Closing, 1943 Oct.-Dec.
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Sept.-1945 Mar.
    - Chain Breaks, commercials, 1943 July-Sept.
    - Spot announcements, 1943 July-1945 Mar.
    - 5 minute news and spots
      - WWJ, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - KMOX, 1944 Aug.-Dec.
      - KFBI, 1944 Aug.-Dec.
      - WOOD, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WFBM, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WISN, 1944 Aug.-Sept.
      - KRNT, 1943 Nov.-1945 Jan.
      - WJR, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
      - WTAM, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
      - KDKA, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
      - WCAU, 1943 July-1944 Sept.
    - WCAU, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 246)
      - WTAR, 1944 Aug.-Dec.
      - WSIX, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WSB, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
      - WBT, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WCSC, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
      - WTMA, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WSB, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WMOB, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WDSU, 1944 July-Sept.
      - Texas State Network, 1943 July-1944 Mar.
    - 15 minute news and spots
      - KTUL, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - KMBC, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - KTAR, 1944 Nov.-1945 Jan.
      - KSL, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - KOA, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - WJAS, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WGR, 1944 Jan.-1945 Jan.
      - KYW, 1944 Feb.-1945 Apr.
      - WCKY, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WGAR, 1944 Aug.-Oct.
      - WGAR, 1944 Oct.-1945 Jan. (Reel 247)
    - Spot announcements, 1944 July-1945 Feb.
    - 15 minute news program
      - WCTN, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WCFL, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WGN, 1944 Aug.-Nov.
      - WMAQ, 1943 Aug.-1944 Mar.
      - WOR, 1943 June-1945 Jan.
        [Apr. 7-July 30 missing]
      - WHBQ, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
      - WSMB, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
      - WQAM, 1945 Jan.
    - Pacific Blue Network, 15 minutes, News program, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
    - Pacific Blue Network, 15 minutes, What's Doing Ladies?, 1944 June-1945 Jan.
    - Texas Quality Network, Early Birds, 1944 July-1945 Jan.
    - WRNL Mail Bag Program, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
    - WAPI Hayloft Jamboree, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan.
    - WLW Victory Girl program, 1943 June-1944 May
    - 10 minute news program, WSGN, 1943 July-1944 Feb.
  - Lever Brothers (Reel 259)
    - Auditions, Lux Soap Revue, 1930
    - V.E. Meadows Beauty School, 1931 July 28
      [See reel 244 for May 4-Oct. 21 scripts]
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    - Broadway Matinee, 1943-1944
      [See reels 205, 237-239 for rest of scripts; no broadcast on June 6, 1944--D-Day]
  - Mentholatum
    - Commercials, WSGN, 1944 Jan.-Mar.
    - Iowa Barn Dance Frolic, WHO, 1943 Aug.-Nov.
    - Commercials, WHO, 1943 July-1944 May
    - Commercials, station breaks, 1942, 1945
    - Commercials, station breaks, 1945 (Reel 260)
    - Commercials, station breaks, 1945 (Reel 261)
  - Fanny Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, station breaks, 1943 Nov.-1945
    - Commercials, station breaks, 1945 (Reel 262)
  - Standard Brands
    - Mary Marlin, 1943 Sept.-1945 Apr.
  - Lamont-Corliss
    - Pond's creams, 1943 July-1944 June
  - Shell Oil
    - Commercials, 1945 Jan.-Mar.
  - Universal Pictures
    - Commercials, 1942 Dec. 21-22
  - Lever Brothers
    - Vimms, 1944 Mar.
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - Commercials, 1943 May-1944 Jan.
    - Commercials, 1944 Jan.-1945 Oct. (Reel 263)
    - Commercials, 1945 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 264)
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit, syrup and molasses, 1945
  - J.B. Williams
    - Glider, WTIC, 1943 Sept.-1945 Dec.
    - Glider, Wm. L. Shirer, 1943 Dec.-1945 Dec.
      [Many dates missing]
    - Glider, WQXR, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
    - Glider, WQXR, 1944 Jan.-June (Reel 265)
  - Ward Baking Co.
    - Aunt Hannah's Enriched Bread, 1943 Apr.-1944 Dec.
    - Judy & Jane, 1943 Jan.-July
    - Spot announcements, 1943-1944
    - Various stations, 1943-1944
    - Various stations, 1943-1944 (Reel 266)
    - Dick Tracy
      - WENR, 1944 Apr.-1945 May
      - WTRY, 1944 Oct.-1945 May
      - WNAB, 1944 May-1945 May
      - WJZ, 1944 Apr.-1945 May
      - WNBC, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WCOL, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WXYZ, 1944 Oct.-1945 May
      - KXOK, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - KQV, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WWVA, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WAGE, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WFIL, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WORC, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WKIP, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WLEU, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WICI, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WHDH, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WHOT, 1944 Oct.-1945 Mar.
      - WHOT, 1945 Apr.-May (Reel 267)
      - WSGN, 1945 Feb.-May
      - WFMJ, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WJHP, 1944 Oct.-1945 May
      - WFIL, 1945 May
      - WJW, 1944 Sept.-1945 May
      - WORC, 1945 May-Aug.
      - WLEU, 1945 May-Aug.
      - WAGE, 1945 May-Aug.
      - WENR, 1945 May-Aug.
      - WTRY, 1945 May-Aug.
      - WFMJ, 1945 May
      - WSGN, 1945 May-July
    - Spot announcements
      - WXYZ, 1943 May-1944 Dec.
      - WBNS, 1943 May-1944 May
      - WSBC, 1944
      - WSBT, 1943 Oct.-1944 Dec.
      - WITH, 1943 May-1944 Dec.
      - WGES, 1944 Sept.-Dec.
        [Polish Dinner Bell, Mrs. Emily Rewicx]
      - WNAC, 5 minute, 1944 Feb.-Dec.
      - WNLC, 5 minute, 1944 Feb.-Dec.
      - WWNY, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec.
      - WKBN, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Jan.
      - WKBN, 5 minute, 1944 Jan.-1944 Dec. (Reel 268)
      - WFMJ, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec.
      - WFBR, 5 minute, 1944 Jan.-Dec.
      - WGES, 15 minute, 1944 Jan.-May
    - Spot announcements, 1943 May-Sept.
      - WOR, 15 minute, 1943 Sept.-1944 Dec.
      - WBBM, 1944 May-Dec.
      - WJR, 10 minute, 1943 Oct.-1944 July
      - KMOX, 1943 June-Sept.
      - KMOX, WJAX, 1943 Sept.-1944 Dec.
      - WFBR, 1943 Dec.-1944 Feb.
      - WFBR, 15 minute, 1944 Feb.-1944 Dec. (Reel 269)
      - WAPI, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec.
      - KSD, 15 minute, 1943 June-1944 May
      - WGN, 15 minute, 1944 Apr.-Oct.
      - WBNS, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 July
      - WABC, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 June
      - WJW, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec.
      - WCBM, 15 minute, 1943 Oct.-1944 Dec.
      - WMBR, 15 minute, 1944 Oct.-Dec.
      - WWJ, 15 minute, 1944 Dec.-1945 Feb.
      - WHKC, 30 minute, 1944 Aug.-Dec.
      - WNAC, 5 minute, 1945 Jan.-Feb.
      - WCAO, 5 minute, 1946 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 270)
      - WNLC, 5 minute, 1945
      - WKBN, 5 minute, 1945
      - WFMJ, 5 minute, 1945
      - WWNY, 5 minute, 1945
      - WMBR, 10 minute, 1945 Jan.-June
      - KDKA, 10 minute, 1945 Jan.-June
      - WDEV, 1945 July-Dec.
      - WOR, 15 minute, 1945
      - WWJ, 15 minute, 1944 Feb.-1945 June
        [Dates missing]
      - WFBR, 5 minute, 1945 Jan.-1946 May
      - WFBR, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-1946 May
      - WJW, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-June
      - WIBG, 15 minute, 1945 Oct.-Dec.
      - WBBM, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Aug.
      - KMOX, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Aug.
      - WGES, 15 minute, 1945
      - WAPI, 15 minute, 1945
      - WXYZ, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-July
      - WCBM, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Mar.
      - WITH, 15 minute, 1945 jan.-1946 Jan.
      - WSBC, 15 minute, 1945
      - WJAX, 15 minute, 1945
      - WSBT, 15 minute, 1945
      - WHKC, 15 minute, 1945
      - WWSW, Aunt Hannah, 1945 Jan.-Oct.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 275)
    - The Ballantine Show, 1945 Jan.-Sept.
    - His Honor, The Barber, 1945 oct.-Dec.
    - Commercials, 1945 Apr. 12
    - Milena Miller, 1945 Apr. 18
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Commercials, 1945 Jan.-1946 Apr.
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Ford promotion spots, 1945 Sept. 15
    - Stars of the Future, 1945
    - Frances Greer, 1945 Apr.-June
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Earl Wilson Show, 1945 Jan.-Mar.
    - Earl Wilson Show, 1945 Mar.-July (Reel 276)
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Bill Henry News, 1945
      [Missing Jan. 1, Dec. 20 broadcasts]
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Show, 1945
      [No broadcast Apr. 12]
    - Bing Crosby, 1945 Jan.-June
    - Edward Everett Hale, 1945 July-Sept.
    - Frank Morgan, 1945 Oct.-Dec.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1945 Jan.-Feb.
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1945 Feb.-Dec. (Reel 277)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1945 Dec. 17-31 (Reel 278)
    - Vimms, Deal spots, 1944 Feb.-Mar.
      [See also reel 237]
    - Vimms, Deal live copy, 1944 Feb.-Mar.
    - Vimms, Deal Hitch-Hikes, 1944 Jan.-Feb.
    - Vimms, Bright Horizons--Frank Sinatra, 1944 Jan.-Oct.
  - Mentholatum
    - Recorded spots, 1944 Nov. 13
    - Mentholatum Mountaineers, 1945 Mar.-1946 Jan.
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    - Fred Waring, 1945 Jan.-May
      [See reel 308 for Jan. 1 broadcast]
  - Reader's Digest
    - Selecciones (Spanish edition), 1945 July 31
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Commercials, 1944 Oct. 15
      [See reel 239 for rest of year]
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1945 Jan.-Nov.
    - Raymond Paige, A Battle of Music, 1945 Dec.
  - Seven-Up
    - Fresh Up Show, 1945 Apr.-Dec.
    - Promotion spots, 1945 Aug. 15
    - Dealer spots, 1945 Aug.-Nov.
  - Skol, Skat spots, 1945 Mar.-May (Reel 279)
  - Standard Brands
    - Chase & Sanborn, Edgar Bergen, 1945
    - Chase & Sanborn, Francis Langford, 1945 June-Aug.
    - Tenderleaf Tea, spot announcements, 1941 Jan.
    - Tenderleaf Tea, Tommy Dorsey, 1945 June-Sept.
      [See reel 343 for June 10]
    - Tenderleaf Tea, Fred Allen, 1945 Oct.-Dec.
    - Tenderleaf Tea, Fred Allen, 1945 Dec. (Reel 280)
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, Mary Marlin, 1945 Jan.-Apr.
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, One Man's Family, 1945 Jan.-June
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, One Man's Family, 1945 June-Dec. (Reel 281)
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, spot announcements, 1945 July 31
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Commercials, 1945 Feb. 11
      [See reel 278 for rest of broadcasts]
  - Textron
    - This is Helen Hayes, 1945 Feb.-July
    - Textron Theatre, 1945 Sept.-Dec.
      [See reel 283 for Sept. 29]
  - Ward Baking
    - Sales meeting (not to be broadcast), 1945 Jan. 30
    - Tennessee Jed, 1945
      [Through episode 17]
    - Tennessee Jed, 1945 (Reel 282)
      [Episodes 18-on; missing episodes 31-34]
  - Textron (Reel 283)
    - Textron Theatre, 1945 Sept. 29
  - J.B. Williams
    - Wm. L. Shirer, news, 1945
    - Commercials, 1945
    - Talks, 1945 Jan.-Aug.
  - W.F. Young, Inc. (Absorbine Jr.) (Reel 305)
    - Happy Endings, sample radio script by John A. Carter, 1946 Jan. 14
  - Reader's Digest
    - Commercials, 1946 Jan. 15
  - Shell Oil
    - Commercials, 1946 Apr. 19
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - His Honor the Barber, Barry Fitzgerald, 1946 Jan.-Apr.
  - U. S. Brewers' Foundation
    - Commercials, 1946 Aug. 21
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Spot announcements, 1946 Feb.-Dec.
  - Fannie Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, 1946
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Bob Crosby Show, 1946 Jan.-July
    - The Ford Show, 1946 Sept.-Dec.
  - Johns-Manville Company (Reel 306)
    - Bill Henry News, 1946
  - Irving Trust
    - Spot announcements, 1946 Nov. 12
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Music Hall, 1946
      [Missing Sept. 26]
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - Your Neighbor Lady, commercials, 1946 Oct.-Dec.
  - Lever Brothers (Reel 307)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1946 Mar.-Dec.
      [No summer broadcasts; see reel 309 for first 3 pages of Mar. 11 broadcast]
  - Ford Motor Company
    - The Ford Show, 1946 Dec.
    - Ford dealer spots, 1946 Oct. 29-31
  - Mentholatum
    - Recorded spots, 1946
    - Mentholatum Mountaineers, 1946 Jan.
    - Mentholatum Mountaineers, 1946 Jan.-Feb. (Reel 308)
  - Northern Trust
    - The Northerners, #788, 1946 Nov. 6
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    - Fred Waring, 1945 Jan. 4
      [See reel 278 for rest of program]
  - Parker Pen
    - Information Please, 1941 Oct.-Dec.
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses, 1946 Jan.-Apr.
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - 15-Minute News, 1946
  - Pharma-Craft
    - Fresh deodorant, spots, 1946 May 17
  - Seven-Up
    - Fresh Up Show, 1946 Jan.-June
    - Dealer spots, 1946 Feb.-Apr.
  - Standard Brands (Reel 309)
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, One Man's Family, 1946
    - Spot announcements, 1945 Oct.-1946 Feb.
    - Chase & Sanborn (Reel 310)
      - Edgar Bergen, 1946
        [No summer broadcasts]
      - Alec Templeton, 1946 June-Aug.
        [Summer substitute for Edgar Bergen]
      - Fred Allen, 1946
      - Tommy Dorsey, 1946 June-Aug.
        [Summer substitute for Fred Allen]
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1946 Aug.-Sept. (Reel 311)
    - Television shows, Hour Glass, 1946 May-Dec.
      [No broadcast Sept. 26, Nov. 21]
    - Television shows, Face to Face, commercials, 1946 June-Dec.
  - Ward Baking
    - Aunt Hannah's Bread, spots, 1945 Jan.
    - Spot announcements, 1946 (Reel 312)